I own talent agency group, have a chain of photography studios as well.
Can you give me a split of the revenue between the modeling agency and the photo studio?
The photo business is about just a little over $1 million.
And the rest is...
The 2.4 is through the agency.
Okay.
Got it.
Net margin on photo, that 25 to 30% depending on the package.
Okay.
And what are you making on the 2.4?
That another 250.
Okay.
Got it.
So it's half the margin.
If the photo studio disappeared, would your life be easier?
If the agency disappeared, my life will be easier.
What part of the modeling agency business do you not like?
Fact that you can't control the outcome for all the talent.
You're like, if you're ugly, you're ugly.
There's nothing I can do, right?
If you had half your time back, would the problems that you're dealing with either of
these businesses be solvable?
You only have enough time to maintain them, not grow them.
Both of them make the same profit.
I would say that modeling agency scales easier, but you sound like you hate that.
And so pick whichever one you want, get all the time back and go all in on that.
That means you stay the pack.
You pick and then you commit.